indextank.com 2014-02-10

# Privacy Policy - Searchify

Searchify LLC ("Searchify," "we," or "us") knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Searchify when you access the Searchify Service (including through the websites of our partners), how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Use [link].

## Information We Collect

**Our Service** : We may receive personally identifiable information about you through our website or through our partners who use our Service (including by embedding our code on their websites or through our APIs) to improve the offerings of their websites. When you visit such websites, your browser may send us certain information about you as described below. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses. We may also retain any search query strings you send through the Service, including on a partner website. 

**Cookies Information** : We may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets learn about your behavior and usage patterns. A cookie may also convey anonymous information about how you browse the a partner website to us. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

**Log File Information** : Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you access the Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

**Clear Gifs Information** : When you access the Service, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your Searchify account is collected using these clear gifs. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our Service, and make Searchify better for our users and partners.

## How We Use Your Information

We use the information that we collect to operate and maintain our Service, and to help our partners improve their online offerings. 

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) monitor the effectiveness of our Service and the offerings of our partners; (b) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (c) diagnose or fix technology problems;.

## How We Share Your Information

**Personally Identifiable Information:** Searchify will not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to others. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Searchify (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or portions of our business, Customer, Email and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, anonymous and/or aggregated search queries, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Searchify services and those of our partners. Non-personally identifiable information may be stored indefinitely.

## How We Protect Your Information

Searchify is concerned with protecting your privacy and data, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Searchify or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Credit card information that you disclose to us is stored by secure payment providers.

## Compromise of Personal Information

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Searchify will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

## Your Choices About Your Information

You can review and correct the information about you that Searchify keeps on file by contacting us directly at support@searchify.com. 

## Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Searchify does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to Searchify. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@searchify.com.

## Notification Procedures

It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on the Service, as determined by Searchify in its sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on the Service to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at support@searchify.com.
